It's a week later and people are still talking about this damn interview, but I just wanted to bring something to the foreground.
I've been doing interviews, like as an interviewer, since 2003.
I was a hip-hop journalist and I wrote for XXL, the source for allhiphop.com.
I was also a radio host on Sirius Satellite Radio.
Um, I've also had a podcast for six years.
I'm also now a radio host again.
And so I am an expert interviewer.
So I just wanted to point out the comedy of people not only doubting my experience on that show as an interviewee,
but also forgetting that I am an expert interviewer who is not only judging it as an interviewee,
but as an interviewer and saying this one nit.
I forgot, I was also a host on MTV too.
So while I have you, if you want to hear me talk about my experiences and give you the comedies and give you the truths,
then I hope to see you at the Unlikable Tour.
I will be in Baltimore, Maryland on May 10th, 11th, and 12th at the Baltimore Comedy Factory.
Ticket link in bio or go to amandaseals.com.
Let's sell these shows out.
Let's support a real one.
I'm really good at comedy.
That was me tooting my own horn.